Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: May 04, 2018

We value the privacy of those who use our service. We process personal data in accordance with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and the data protection laws of Switzerland.

This Privacy Policy covers the collection, use and disclosure of information that may be collected any time you interact with the Teamup Calendar “Service” (e.g. when you visit our web site, use our calendaring service, or communicate with Teamup support, etc.). Teamup undertakes all common and reasonable precautions to protect user information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

This Privacy Policy amends and supplements our [Terms of Service](https://www.teamup.com/terms-of-service/) and our [Data Processing Agreement](https://www.teamup.com/dpa/). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may discontinue the use of Teamup and delete your calendar.

### 1\. Personal Information

Teamup collects contact details (e.g. your email address) and other personal information during the calendar creation process.

None of the personal information Teamup collects will be shared with third parties, unless

* you have explicitly agreed to it.
* we need to share your data to fulfill your Service requests.
* Teamup believes to be required to do so by law.

### 2\. Calendar Data

Teamup collects calendar data (e.g. event date, event time, event location, event participants, event descriptions, etc.).

None of the calendar data is shared with third parties unless

* the calendar owner explicitly allows or asks for it.
* we need to share your data to fulfill your Service requests.
* Teamup believes to be required to do so by law.

### 3\. Logging

Teamup collects a wide range of log information for the purposes of monitoring, debugging, and improving the Service. This includes automatically generated problem, performance, network analysis and general usage reports, as well as logs of the connections and queries made to Teamup’s servers (including the involved IP addresses), as well as analytical data about the usage of Teamup’s website. Teamup makes use of “cookies” in order to provide its Service.

None of the logging data is shared with third parties unless Teamup believes to be required to do so by law. Teamup may share summarized usage data about the Service with third parties for marketing purposes.

### 4\. User Communications

Teamup collects and archives mail, email, data entered into web forms, and any other communication you send to Teamup for the purpose of processing and answering your requests and improving Teamup’s Service. Teamup may share user communication with third parties as needed to operate and improve the Service.

### 5\. Location of Data

Data is hosted in Oregon (United States), Dublin (Ireland), and Zurich (Switzerland).

### 6\. Changes to this Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change anytime. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy. The latest version of this Privacy Policy is always available at [http://www.teamup.com/privacy-policy](https://www.teamup.com/privacy-policy/).

TABLE OF CONTENTS

Copyright © 2014 - 2024 Teamup Solutions AG. All Rights Reserved.
